Fridge is empty, dandries are chilled.
One sad pickle and some diet coke.
We swore we'd shop but we slept instead.
Now we're starvin' full of dread.
Stomach's rumbling, now the clock strikes six.
We argue and we disagree, lick and mix.
You want sushi, I want fries and shakes.
Round and round, another fight you undertake.
Chun-Li!
Oh Chun-Li!
Meet us on my phone.
We scroll for an hour.
You say you're vegan now You want a cauliflower?
I just want burritos Or maybe some wings Why does dinner Turn to a million things?
We had breakfast cold And lunch was late They say food brings luck But this might bring hate
Stomach's rumbling, now the clock strikes six.
We argue and we disagree, mic and mix.
You want sushi, I want flies and shakes.
Round and round, another bite you want to take.
Can we eat?
Oh, can we eat?
Oh, tell me